Lucía López Liñares

Storyboard Artist



📺 www.linkedin.com/in/lucialopezlulo 年

Storyboard Show Reel <</p>

Direction Show Reel 🗢

👸 Storyboard Portfolio 😓

lucialopezlinares.lulo@gmail.com

+34 646 23 91 93

Spain

After more than 6 years working within the animation industry, I've had the opportunity to try different roles: concept artist, storyboard artist, 2D animator, supervisor, and director.

I love finding the best way to show a story, the perfect shot or expression to convey a feeling, and make sure everything fits so the audience can relate, enjoy, and learn, just like I did when I was a kid... And still do!

SOFTWARE

- Storyboard Pro
- Animate (Flash)
- Harmony
- Photoshop
- Q 0 0
- Premiere
- D. D. D.
- Shotgrid

EXPERIENCE

Dec. 2023 - Present

STORYBOARD ARTIST

Cleo & Cuquín (3D digital series) Ánima Kitchent

Jul. 2022 - Mar. 2023 | 9 months

ASSISTANT DIRECTOR, STORYBOARD SUPERVISOR

Annie & Carola (2D TV series)

Mondo TV Studios

Mar. 2021 - Jun. 2022 | 1 year, 3 months

DIRECTOR

Plum The Super Witch (2D digital series) Increditales (3D digital series) Amuse Animation

Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2021 | 3 months

STORYBOARD ARTIST

Disco Dragon (2D TV series) Mondo TV Studios

• Dec. 2017 - Aug. 2019 | 1 year, 8 months

2D ANIMATION DEPARTMENT SUPERVISOR

Asubío Media

Feb. 2016 - Dec. 2017 | 1 year, 10 months

STORYBOARD ARTIST, 2D ANIMATOR, CONCEPT ARTIST

Multiple 2D digital projects (series and music videos)

Asubío Media

SKIUS

PROBLEM SOLVING ATTENTION TO DETAIL COMMUNICATION TEAM WORK ADAPTABILITY STORYTELLING

EDUCATION

Showrunner: creating and producing series

Postgraduate Expert Program in Character Design

2013-2014 Character creation for 3D animation

IHMAN 3D School

2010-2011 Advanced 2D and 3D animation

Nexofilms Granada (Spain)

2007-2013 | Fine Arts Degree

University of Granada (Spain)

MORE INFORMATION

- · Languages: Spanish and Galician (Native), English (B2)
- Production Manager short film "Mércores de Cinza"
- Production Assistant documentary "As anguías non levan roupa"
- Production Assistant short film "Sereas"